{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-4",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 4",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "grade5",
    "unit4",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 4: Our free-time activities",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "watch cartoons",
      "answer": "xem phim hoạt hình",
      "speak": "watch cartoons"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "play the violin",
      "answer": "chơi đàn vi-ô-lông",
      "speak": "play the violin"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "surf the Internet",
      "answer": "lướt Internet",
      "speak": "surf the internet"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "water the flowers",
      "answer": "tưới hoa",
      "speak": "water the flowers"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "go for a walk",
      "answer": "đi dạo",
      "speak": "go for a walk"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "read a book",
      "answer": "đọc sách",
      "speak": "read a book"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "listen to music",
      "answer": "nghe nhạc",
      "speak": "listen to music"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "ride a bike",
      "answer": "đi xe đạp",
      "speak": "ride a bike"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "weekend",
      "answer": "cuối tuần",
      "speak": "weekend"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "volleyball",
      "answer": "bóng chuyền",
      "speak": "volleyball"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "entertain",
      "answer": "giải trí",
      "speak": "entertain"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "shopping",
      "answer": "mua sắm",
      "speak": "shopping"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "cooking",
      "answer": "nấu ăn",
      "speak": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "roller skating",
      "answer": "trượt patin",
      "speak": "roller skating"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "always",
      "answer": "luôn luôn",
      "speak": "always"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "sometimes",
      "answer": "đôi khi",
      "speak": "sometimes"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "usually",
      "answer": "thường xuyên",
      "speak": "usually"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "rarely",
      "answer": "hiếm khi",
      "speak": "rarely"
    }
  ]
}